fast2sms.com 2017-06-25

# Unlimited Free SMS in India | Free Group SMS | Free Mobile Recharge | Free SMS Site | Send Free SMS | Free SMS to Mobile

Fast2SMS.com takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.You are advised to please read the Privacy Policy carefully. By accessing the services provided by Fast2SMS.com you agree to the collection and use of your data by Fast2SMS in the manner provided in this Privacy Policy.

if you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should contact Fast2SMS Customer Support Desk at [support@fast2sms.com](mailto:support@fast2sms.com)

**What this Privacy Policy Covers**

  * -This Privacy Policy covers Fast2SMS.com treatment of personally identifiable information that Fast2SMS collects when you are on the site   

**What information is or may be collected from you**   
We will automatically receive and collect certain anonymous information in standard usage logs through our Web server, including computer-identification information obtained from "cookies," sent to your browser from: 

  * \- an IP address, assigned to the computer which you use 
  * \- the domain server through which you access our service 
  * \- the type of computer you're using 
  * \- the type of web browseryou're using 

We may collect the following personally identifiable information about you: 

  * \- name including first and last name 
  * \- email address 
  * \- mobile phone number 
  * \- opinions of features on our websites. 

**How is this information used**   
We use your email address to send you: 

  * \- password reminder and registration confirmation 
  * \- changes in the service's policy or terms of use 
  * \- event based communications such as order information, renewal notices, invites, reminders etc. 

We use your Mobile number to send you:

  * \- password reminder and Registration confirmation
  * \- special feature updates

We use your personal information to: 

  * \- to get in touch with you in the case of password retrieval and policy changes 
  * \- to provide the services requested by you 

**Information Sharing And disclosure**

We do not share or rent your email addresses or Mobile number with third parties.

**Security**

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information and email address, Mobile Number submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. Your Fast2SMS Account is password protected.No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure.

if you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at   

**Your Preferences to Edit and Delete Your Account Information**

Fast2SMS gives you the ability to edit your fast2sms account information and preferences at any time, including whether you want Fast2SMS to contact you about specials and new products. .

You may request us to delete your account by emailing to [support@fast2sms.com](mailto:support@fast2sms.com.). We send you a 4 digit unique number to your Mobile number, using this you can unsubscribe/delete your account.

Users which are not registered with us will never get any type of notification including spam mails and sms.

**Policy Updates**

We reserve the right to change or update this policy at any time by placing a prominent notice on our site homepage.  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, or by means of a notice on our homepage.

**Contact Information**  
You can contact us at:
